[Music]
little you can with me if you
want it to these expensive these is red
bottoms these is bloody shoes hit the
school I can get them both I don't want
to choose and I'm quick cut a off
so don't get comfortable Bo look I don't
dance now I make money moov say I don't
got to dance I make money moov if I see
you I don't speak that means I don't
with you I'm a boss you a r I
make bloody mov now she say she going to
do what who let's find out and see C be
you know where I'm at you know where I
be you in the club just to party I'm
there I get paid a fee I'll be in
another bank so much I know they tired
of me honestly don't give a about
who in F of me Dr to mixtap in 6 months
we working this hard as me I don't
bother with these hoes don't let these
hoes bother me they see pictures they
say goost I'm who they trying to
be look I might just telling some bab I
might just show with your boo I might
just feel on your babe my feel
like a leg he want to swim with his face
I'm like okay I let him get what he want
he buy me e in the new rib when it go
fast as horse I got the trunk in the
front I'm the hottest in the street know
you probably heard of me got a bag and
fix my teeth hope you hoes no a che and
I pay my mama bills I ain't got no time
to chill think these hoes be mad at me
they baby
father little you can with me
if you want to these expensive these is
red bottoms these is bloody shoes hit
the school I can get them both I don't
want to Cho and I'm quick cuz a
so don't get comfortable look I don't
dance now I make money moves say I don't
got to dance I make money move if I see
you I don't speak that means I don't
with you I'm a boss you a work
I make bloody mov if you a
you get popped you a goofy you a up
don't you come around my way you can't
hang around my block and I just took my
account so I'm rich I'm rich I'm rich my
hand above my hip I bet you dip he dip
she dip I say I get the money and go
this is hot like a stove my
glitter is gold tell that little
her roll I just a r no roll I just came
up in a r I need to fill up the tank no
I need to fill up the safe I need to let
all these hoes know they none of the
to say I go to dinner and steak
only the real can relay I used to live
in the peace now it's a crib with the
gay R got charms the life the hard to
let these know just in case
these hoes for I just want to check the
M another Che that little you can
with me if you want to these
expensive these is red bottoms these is
bloody shoes hit the school I can get
them both I don't want to choose and I'm
quick cutting so don't get
comfortable look I don't dance now I
make money moves say I don't got to
dance I make money move if I see you and
I don't speak that means I with you
I'm a boss to a work I make bloody
moves blood
[Music]